JENNIFER COOPER

Over 4 years of experience of working as a graphic designer in IT industry. Brilliance in technical, time-management, and problemsolving skills. Like to work as a motivational team leader and help

youremailname@gmail.com +0 000 123 4567 www.domainnamehere.com

EXPERIENCE

XLOGICS, UNITED STATES

Graphic Designer

2016 - 2018

Met short deadlines and satisfied most clients with my designing skills throughout. Lead a team of 8 designers and designed logos and templates for web and mobile applications.

BYTE TECHNOLOGIES, UNITED STATES

Graphic Designer

2014 - 2016

Completed projects after coordinating with outside agencies. Led design workshops and participated in professional design societies.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF MIAMI, USA

UI/UX Master Degree

2012 - 2014

Got nominated for outstanding academic accomplishment award. The final thesis project helped me earn honor and job offers from top companies.

FULL SAIL UNIVERSITY, USA

Bachelor of Graphic Design

2008 - 2012

My CGPA was 3.8 throughout my undergrad program. Several times I was appreciated for completing assignments well before deadlines.

A PROFESSIONAL GRAPHIC DESIGNER



PROFESSIONALSKILLS

ADOBE PHOTOSHOP

ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR

ADOBE XD

FIGMA

SKETCH

INTERESTS&HOBBIES

- TRAVELING
- PHOTOGRAPHY
- SNOOKER
- VIDEOGAMES
- READING